

CONTACT

9 Bhakkar, Punjab Pakistan

+92 3142588002

M mh2588002@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/muhammad -huzaifa-0795142b6/

TECHNICAL & SOFT SKILLS

- AutoCAD
- MS Office
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketchup
- Revit
- 3ds Max
- ❖ As Built Drawings
- ❖ Civil Bill Verification

LANGUAGES

English: Intermediate

Urdu: Fluent

Korean: Basic

MUHAMMAD HUZAIFA

Draftsman | Support Officer

PROFILE

I am a Civil Supervisor, AutoCAD Draftsman and Support Officer with experience in various engineering roles. I started my career at The Engineers and Constructors Pvt Ltd., where I assisted in civil supervisor. Later, I joined Design 19 Pvt Ltd. as an AutoCAD Draftsman, creating detailed interior drawings and planning furniture designs. Later, I joined Habib Bank Limited Pvt Ltd. Engineering Department, working on preparation of B.O.Q., measurement sheets, contractors bill verification, drawings, financial approvals, and vendor management across multiple projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DRAFTSMAN & SUPPORT OFFICER

Habib Bank Limited - Karachi Feb 2020 - Mar 2024

Contract Under below mentioned companies. AAA Facility Management WEMCO Engineering. New Khan Company.

DRAFTSMAN

Design 19 Pvt Ltd – Karachi Jan 2019 – Dec 2019

CIVIL SUPERVISOR

The Engineers and Constructors. Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA OF ASSOCIATE ENGINEERING - CIVIL

2018

Govt College of Technology – Bhakkar

MATRIC - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Govt. Model High School – Bhakkar 2015